Finding Aid for the Bob Brown Papers LSC.0723
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Rose Brown's diary. (Box 60)
- We saw it coming by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 60)
- "Brazil". Vol. 33 No.1. (Box 61)
- "Cora Brown" notepad/diary. (Box 61)
- Backslidders - one act play by Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 61)
- Brown's Brazilian identity card. (Box 61)
- Dance book correspondence. (Box 61)
- Dance book notes. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Argentina. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Bolivia. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Brazil. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Chile. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Colombia. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Costa Rica. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Cuba. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Dominican Republic. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Ecuador. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - El Salvador. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Guatemala. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Haiti. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Paraguay. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Peru. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Puerto Rico. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Uruguay. (Box 61)
- Latin American dancebook chapter - Venezuela. (Box 61)
- Middle-West memories (1) by Cora L. Brown. (Box 61)
- Middle-West memories (2) by Cora L. Brown. (Box 61)
- Notes on dances by country. (Box 61)
- Rose Brown book contract for "In the land of coffee". (Box 61)
- Timothy Commonstock - one act play by Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 61)
- To vote or not to vote. (Box 61)
- Accounting Notebook. (Box 62)
- Association of Inter-American Museums -- Proposals, Correspondence, Notes, Sketches, Clippings. (Box 62)
- Children's Drawings. (Box 62)
- Clippings - Literary. (Box 62)
- Clippings - Miscellaneous. (Box 62)
- Clippings - re: Brazil. (Box 62)
- Clippings - Visual Material (Advertising, Cartoons, Typography). (Box 62)
- Correspondence. (Box 62)
- Correspondence. (Box 62)
- Correspondence -- Biographical Letter to Upton Sinclair. (Box 62)
- Correspondence -- New Llano. (Box 62)
- Dedication -- To My Son Jonathan (note). (Box 62)
- Incomplete Manuscripts. (Box 62)
- Manuscript -- A Time to Love and a Time to Leave by Carlton Brown. (Box 62)
- Manuscript -- Brown Family Robinson, an autobiographical novel by Rose and Bob Brown (various pages). (Box 62)
- Manuscript -- Down to Rio - biographical notes by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 62)
- Manuscript -- Kloof-dwellers in Zuzuland. (Box 62)
- Manuscript -- Living Dangerously. (Box 62)
- Manuscript -- Notes on Petropolis. (Box 62)
- Manuscript -- Settling Down Begins at Sixty - by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 62)
- Manuscript -- We Saw It Coming - by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 62)
- Notes -- Ten Commandments for Co-Operative Colonies. (Box 62)
- Paul F. Hoag Dealer Catalog. (Box 62)
- Poetry. (Box 62)
- Publication -- Chapter 32 - Fruity News From Heaven. (Box 62)
- Publication -- Okay, America - Let's Go! (in International Literature). (Box 62)
- Publication -- Them Asses by Bob Brown. (Box 62)
- Recipes. (Box 62)
- Recipes -- Burgers. (Box 62)
- Royalty Statements and Correspondence. (Box 62)
- Scrap Paper / Notes. (Box 62)
- Biographical Statement -- Personal Collection of "Bob Brown," Author, Editor, Publisher, and World-Traveller. (Box 63)
- Book Jacket -- Amazon Adventures of Two Children, by Rose Brown. (Box 63)
- Clippings -- Amazing Amazon. (Box 63)
- Clippings -- Biographical. (Box 63)
- Clippings -- Miscellaneous. (Box 63)
- Clippings -- Visual Materials. (Box 63)
- Correspondence. (Box 63)
- Correspondence -- Letter from William Carlos Williams (pp. 2-folder 3 of 3). (Box 63)
- Correspondence -- Mary Wilson. (Box 63)
- Diary (author unknown). (Box 63)
- Gastronomy -- Notes, Clippings. (Box 63)
- Gastronomy -- Recipes. (Box 63)
- Gastronomy -- Wine Making Pamphlets. (Box 63)
- Manuscript -- "R" in Season, Too. (Box 63)
- Manuscript -- Bee-Lieve It or Not!, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 63)
- Manuscript -- Buck-Up on Your Continental English. (Box 63)
- Manuscript -- Coin of the Realm. (Box 63)
- Manuscript -- In a Blur of Babies. (Box 63)
- Manuscript -- Money You Can't Spend. (Box 63)
- Manuscript -- The Complete Book of Beer (chapter outline). (Box 63)
- Manuscript -- The Lady Tourist. (Box 63)
- Manuscript -- Why Authors Should Always Remain in Bed, by Herman Spector. (Box 63)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 63)
- Note -- On Becoming a Father. (Box 63)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 63)
- Clippings -- from Punch. (Box 64)
- Clippings -- miscellaneous. (Box 64)
- Clippings -- re: bullfighting. (Box 64)
- Clippings -- reviews of Two Children of Brazil, by Rose Brown. (Box 64)
- Clippings -- The Perfect Squelch. (Box 64)
- Clippings -- visual material. (Box 64)
- Correspondence. (Box 64)
- Correspondence -- Langston Hughes. (Box 64)
- Correspondence -- re: 1450-1950. (Box 64)
- Erotica -- HE Magazine; playing cards. (Box 64)
- Gastronomy -- copy of Feeding the Mind, by Lewis Carroll. (Box 64)
- Inventory -- Archaeological Materials. (Box 64)
- Journal Entries and Short Stories. (Box 64)
- Juvenalia. (Box 64)
- Manuscript -- Alpine Symphony, by Rose Brown. (Box 64)
- Manuscript -- At the French Salon, by Rose Brown. (Box 64)
- Manuscript -- Behind the 8 Ball. (Box 64)
- Manuscript -- By Their Gifts Ye Shall Know Them. (Box 64)
- Manuscript -- Come to Coral Beeches. (Box 64)
- Manuscript -- Going Native Right at Home. (Box 64)
- Manuscript -- In Snowy Spain. (Box 64)
- Manuscript -- The Complete History of the Jaquar and the Monkey. (Box 64)
- Manuscript -- Twisty Capello's Last Killing. (Box 64)
- Manuscript -- Two Ghosts With One Stone, by Rose Brown. (Box 64)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 64)
- Original Folders -- annotated. (Box 64)
- Pamphlet -- Chinese Coins Without Currency. (Box 64)
- Poetry. (Box 64)
- Publication -- One White Hour, by Cornelia and Robert Brown. (Box 64)
- Publication -- Shanghai New Year. (Box 64)
- Royalty Statements. (Box 64)
- Transcript -- fortune teller's analysis (analysand unknown). (Box 64)
- Biographical Statement -- Bob, Cora, and Rose Brown. (Box 65)
- Booklet -- Institute of Anthropology and Ethnology, Belem Brazil. (Box 65)
- Clippings -- "Signs of the Times". (Box 65)
- Clippings -- Miscellaneous. (Box 65)
- Clippings -- Punch. (Box 65)
- Clippings -- Visual Materials. (Box 65)
- Correspondence. (Box 65)
- Correspondence -- Letter to Mencken, re: Readies. (Box 65)
- Death Certificate -- Welsey E. Brown. (Box 65)
- Gastronomy -- Clippings. (Box 65)
- Gastronomy -- Published Articles. (Box 65)
- Gastronomy -- Recipes. (Box 65)
- Manuscript -- Brown Family Robinson (outline). (Box 65)
- Manuscript -- Rich Repertoires. (Box 65)
- Manuscript -- Scully's Scrapbook, by Frank Scully. (Box 65)
- Manuscript -- The Red Skins of Munich. (Box 65)
- Manuscript (incomplete) -- biographical notes. (Box 65)
- Note -- on "Gems". (Box 65)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 65)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 65)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 65)
- Original Folders -- annotated. (Box 65)
- Outline -- Mere Man and the Mermaid. (Box 65)
- Poetry. (Box 65)
- Postcards. (Box 65)
- Bibliographical Statement -- Books by Bob Brown. (Box 66)
- Biographical Statements. (Box 66)
- Clippings -- Miscellaneous. (Box 66)
- Clippings -- Visual Materials. (Box 66)
- Correspondence. (Box 66)
- Correspondence -- Albert Stoll re: specs for Reading Machine. (Box 66)
- Correspondence -- Leavinia Kepler. (Box 66)
- Correspondence, Clippings, Notes -- proposal for Autobiography of Art anthology. (Box 66)
- Geneaological Statement. (Box 66)
- Manuscript -- All God's Chillun Got Phobias. (Box 66)
- Manuscript -- Get Rid of Ridder. (Box 66)
- Manuscript -- In the Devi's Dell, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 66)
- Manuscript -- Middle West Memories, by Cora L. Brown. (Box 66)
- Manuscript -- Portrait in Parts, by Rose Brown. (Box 66)
- Manuscript -- The 3-Time Crime. (Box 66)
- Manuscript -- The Face and the Fee. (Box 66)
- Manuscript -- The Patent Adjustable. (Box 66)
- Manuscript, Clippings, Notes -- Giggle Butts. (Box 66)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 66)
- Notes (typed) and Santarem Journal Entries -- by Rose Brown. (Box 66)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 66)
- Original Folders -- annotated. (Box 66)
- Postcards. (Box 66)
- Real Estate Advertisement (draft) -- Estate in Petropolis. (Box 66)
- Biographical Materials -- Cora Brown (Notes, Correspondence). (Box 67)
- Clippings -- Authors Speak for Themselves, NY Herald Tribune. (Box 67)
- Clippings -- Book Review of The Shores of Light, by Edmund Wilson. (Box 67)
- Clippings -- Miscellaneous. (Box 67)
- Clippings -- National Democratic Committee Special Issue. (Box 67)
- Clippings -- Punch. (Box 67)
- Clippings -- re: Reading Machine. (Box 67)
- Clippings -- Visual Materials. (Box 67)
- Clippings, Notes, Records -- Latin American Dances, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 67)
- Correspondence. (Box 67)
- Correspondence -- J.B. Lippincott, co. (Box 67)
- Correspondence -- Knopf, inc. (Box 67)
- Correspondence -- re: Latin American Dances, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 67)
- Correspondence & Documents -- Mystery Writers of America. (Box 67)
- Manuscript -- Taja the Potter, by Rose Brown. (Box 67)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 67)
- Newsletter -- The Federal Writer. (Box 67)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 67)
- Poetry -- typescripts. (Box 67)
- Publication -- CONTEMPO: A Bob Brown Issue. (Box 67)
- Autobiographical Statement -- Dodging the Draft. (Box 68)
- Clippings -- Annals of Crime, New Yorker. (Box 68)
- Clippings -- Miscellaneous. (Box 68)
- Clippings -- Visual Materials. (Box 68)
- CONTEMPO (Bob Brown, Contributing Editor) -- II.2, II.3, III.5. (Box 68)
- Gastronomy -- Clippings, Notes. (Box 68)
- Gastronomy -- Publication: Homemade Hilarity, by Bob Brown (2 copies). (Box 68)
- Gastronomy -- Published Articles. (Box 68)
- Gastronomy -- The Complete Book of Cheese, by Bob Brown (intro. & correspondence). (Box 68)
- Manuscript -- I Don't Die: The Autobiography of Bob Brown (1 p. outline). (Box 68)
- Manuscript -- re: Gems. (Box 68)
- Manuscript -- re: Manhattan (untitled). (Box 68)
- Manuscript -- re: Petropolis Art Dealer (untitled). (Box 68)
- Manuscript -- Seeds of Hope. (Box 68)
- Manuscript -- Why Butchers Wear Straw Hats. (Box 68)
- Manuscript, Notes -- The Amazon Flows On, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 68)
- Manuscripts -- incomplete. (Box 68)
- Manuscripts -- re: rare book collecting (various titles). (Box 68)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 68)
- Notes / Scrap Paper -- financial. (Box 68)
- Notes, Clippings, Correspondence -- re: rare book collecting. (Box 68)
- Poetry -- notes/scrap paper. (Box 68)
- Publication -- Can We Co-Operate (chap. 6-8). (Box 68)
- Publication -- The Hocus Pocus of Book Hoarding. (Box 68)
- Reviews -- Three on a Raft, by Rose Brown. (Box 68)
- Correspondence. (Box 69)
- Correspondence -- Bob Brown to Cora Brown. (Box 69)
- Ephemera -- Kentucky Exchange Singles Listings. (Box 69)
- Ephemera -- Miscellaneous. (Box 69)
- Gastronomy -- Pamphlet on Grape-Culture and Wine-Making. (Box 69)
- Gastronomy -- Recipes, Clippings. (Box 69)
- Magazine -- Policial. (Box 69)
- Manuscript -- Among the Hopheads (1 p.). (Box 69)
- Manuscript -- Bill Haywood, by Rose Brown. (Box 69)
- Manuscript -- Hallelujah, On the Bum (a proletarian hymn). (Box 69)
- Manuscript -- Mr. and Mrs. Brown. (Box 69)
- Manuscript -- My Happy View Valley, by Rose Brown (factual account of events in Tomba de Serra). (Box 69)
- Manuscript -- Raw! Raw! Raw! Oysters, by Bob Brown. (Box 69)
- Manuscript -- The Dying Cowboy, by William Moan. (Box 69)
- Manuscript -- The Little Old Sod Shanty. (Box 69)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 69)
- Notes -- "Broker Brown and His Readies". (Box 69)
- Notes -- autobiographical (typed). (Box 69)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 69)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 69)
- Notes, Drafts, Clippings, Correspondence -- Foolosophy (proverbs). (Box 69)
- Pamphlet -- Preparing for Heaven (a sermon by the Rev. E.E. Iungerich). (Box 69)
- Pamphlet -- Toward New Horizons: The World Beyond the War (Office of War Information). (Box 69)
- Publication -- His Legs Under the Mahogony, by Cora Brown (New Idea Women's Magazine). (Box 69)
- Autobiographical Timeline. (Box 70)
- Clippings -- material on fishing. (Box 70)
- Clippings -- miscellaneous. (Box 70)
- Clippings -- visual material. (Box 70)
- Correspondence. (Box 70)
- Correspondence -- Ralph Hancock and Lowell Brentano (re: "Brentano's Guides"). (Box 70)
- Ephemera. (Box 70)
- Gastronomy -- Publications. (Box 70)
- Gastronomy -- Recipes, Clippings. (Box 70)
- Manuscript -- "Starving in Russia". (Box 70)
- Manuscript -- advertisement for Wizard Oil. (Box 70)
- Manuscript -- Can the Next Generation Forgive This One?. (Box 70)
- Manuscripts -- autobiographical chapters. (Box 70)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 70)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 70)
- Notes, Correspondence, Clippings, Drawings -- Gardening in Brazil. (Box 70)
- Pamphlet -- The Syllabus of a Novel, by Hervey Allen. (Box 70)
- Poetry -- typescripts: "It's Nice in Nice" and "The Monkey's Wedding". (Box 70)
- Advertisement -- The New Caravan Anthology (incl. work by Bob Brown). (Box 71)
- Clippings. (Box 71)
- Clippings -- Visual Materials. (Box 71)
- Correspondence. (Box 71)
- Ephemera. (Box 71)
- Gastronomy -- Clippings, Notes on dieting. (Box 71)
- Gastronomy -- Recipes, Clippings. (Box 71)
- Manuscript -- Little Guy, Big Bomb. (Box 71)
- Manuscript, Correspondence -- Brotherhoods, by Bob Brown. (Box 71)
- Manuscript, Notes -- Down to Rio, by Rose and Bob Brown. (Box 71)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 71)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 71)
- Publication -- from Globe-Gliding. (Box 71)
- Clippings. (Box 72)
- Correspondence. (Box 72)
- Correspondence -- Bob to Cora Brown. (Box 72)
- Correspondence -- from "Grandma Helen". (Box 72)
- Ephemera. (Box 72)
- Manuscript -- Bankers Behind Bars. (Box 72)
- Manuscript -- Readers and Reviewers. (Box 72)
- Manuscript -- The Writer's Plight. (Box 72)
- Manuscripts -- Incomplete. (Box 72)
- Manuscripts, Correspondence -- Short Stories and Articles. (Box 72)
- Notes -- Outline for Autobiography of Art. (Box 72)
- Notes--scrap paper. (Box 72)
- Clippings. (Box 73)
- Clippings -- National Geographic: "The Coasts of Corsica". (Box 73)
- Clippings -- visual material. (Box 73)
- Correspondence. (Box 73)
- Correspondence -- Rose to Bob Brown re: their engagement. (Box 73)
- Ephemera. (Box 73)
- Journal -- daily entries by Cora Brown, trip around the world with Bob, Rose, and Robert. (Box 73)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 73)
- Notes -- health checklists. (Box 73)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 73)
- Notes, Clippings -- "In Love for Keeps". (Box 73)
- Poetry -- "Snow" (juvenalia?). (Box 73)
- Poetry -- "What the Socialists Want" (1 p. ms.). (Box 73)
- Poetry -- notes, drafts. (Box 73)
- Publication -- Sailing in Circles, by Robert Carlton Brown (annotated copy assembled from clippings). (Box 73)
- Clippings. (Box 74)
- Correspondence. (Box 74)
- Drawing -- diagram of a gas lamp. (Box 74)
- Ephemera. (Box 74)
- Manuscript -- Marginalia ("A vague outline for a novel"). (Box 74)
- Manuscript -- The Excellent Dogs (395 pp.). (Box 74)
- Manuscript and Journal Entries -- Amazon Folk Festivals. (Box 74)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 74)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 74)
- Autobiographical Notes -- "Books and I Are Bound". (Box 75)
- Clippings. (Box 75)
- Correspondence. (Box 75)
- Correspondence -- Jonathan Williams re: cancelled publication of 1450-1950, closure of Jargon Press. (Box 75)
- Correspondence -- re: Rose Brown's death, Bob Brown's return to NYC. (Box 75)
- Drafts, Clippings, Correspondence -- The Finger of God, by Rose Brown. (Box 75)
- Ephemera. (Box 75)
- Gastronomy--wine pamphlets. (Box 75)
- Inventory, Financial Papers -- South American Artifacts. (Box 75)
- Manuscript -- Chou Fleur Surprise, by Bob Brown. (Box 75)
- Manuscript -- The alligator out of Norah's [sic] ark. (Box 75)
- Manuscript, Synopsis, Character List -- The Finger of God, by Rose Brown (230 pp.). (Box 75)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 75)
- Notes / Scrap Paper. (Box 75)
- Notes, Clippings, Correspondence, Manuscript -- re: agoraphobia and claustrophobia. (Box 75)
- Pamphlet -- Toward a Bloodless Revolution, by Bob Brown. (Box 75)
- Quotations on love. (Box 75)
- Article--Twentieth Century Impressions of Brazil, by E. Rocquette Pinto. (Box 76)
- Bulletin of the League of American Writers. (Box 76)
- Clippings. (Box 76)
- Clippings -- Visual Materials. (Box 76)
- Correspondence. (Box 76)
- Correspondence -- Letter to Phil Kaplan re: Ezra Pound & 1450-1950. (Box 76)
- Correspondence & Clippings: re Clare Brackett's death. (Box 76)
- Ephemera. (Box 76)
- Gastronomy--pamphlet on Wines & Spirits. (Box 76)
- Inventory--Amazon artifacts. (Box 76)
- List of "Essential Reading". (Box 76)
- Manuscript--"I've never been up against a crowd so hard to handle". (Box 76)
- Manuscript--Azores Ahoy!. (Box 76)
- Manuscript--Dictatorship by Public Utilities. (Box 76)
- Manuscript--Doggie Can You Spare a Bone?. (Box 76)
- Manuscript--Pearl of Praises. (Box 76)
- Manuscript--Quack! Quack!. (Box 76)
- Correspondence: Brown, Allen, and others. (Box 77)
- Gastronomy -- Cooking. (Box 77)
- Gastronomy -- Curry Soup. (Box 77)
- Gastronomy -- Stews are news. (Box 77)
- Mad Mary. (Box 77)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 77)
- Notes--Daily Health Records. (Box 77)
- Notes--scrap paper (folder 1 of 2). (Box 77)
- Notes--scrap paper (folder 2 of 2). (Box 77)
- Pamphlet--The Fundamentals of Fiction Writing, by Will Herman. (Box 77)
- Clippings. (Box 78)
- Correspondence. (Box 78)
- Correspondence, Notes--Petropolis Bone Yard Dispute. (Box 78)
- Correspondence--Ben Hagglund, re: Anvil Press & Can We Co-Operate. (Box 78)
- Correspondence--Financial Records. (Box 78)
- Correspondence--H.H. Lewis, re: New Llano. (Box 78)
- Correspondence--Jack Conroy, re: Anvil Press. (Box 78)
- Diagram--Pinball Game. (Box 78)
- Ephemera. (Box 78)
- Gastronomy--Recipes, Clippings. (Box 78)
- Manuscript, Correspondence, Notes, Clippings--Marginalia, by Bob Brown. (Box 78)
- Manuscript--A Modern Mystery of the Rue Morgue, by Bob Brown. (Box 78)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 78)
- Manuscript--Terry's Guide to Cuba. (Box 78)
- Manuscript--The Marvelous Discoveries of Prof. Jiggs. (Box 78)
- Manuscript--The Mysterious Battle (juvenalia?). (Box 78)
- Manuscript--The Spiritual Boot-Legger. (Box 78)
- Clippings. (Box 79)
- Clippings--Visual Materials. (Box 79)
- Correspondence. (Box 79)
- Correspondence. (Box 79)
- Correspondence -- Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 79)
- Ephemera. (Box 79)
- Gastronomy -- A World of Dishes and Drinks (checklist). (Box 79)
- Gastronomy -- Interview on Dieting with Bob, Rose, and Cora Brown. (Box 79)
- Gastronomy -- Lists of Cookbooks and Articles by the Browns. (Box 79)
- Memo for In Fact, re: Lenin. (Box 79)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 79)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 79)
- Pamphlets--book collecting. (Box 79)
- Passport--Cora L. Brown. (Box 79)
- Poetry--Drinking the Water of My Bath, by Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 79)
- Poetry--The Aquarium Keeper, by Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 79)
- Poetry--Wasting Words, Perhaps, by Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 79)
- Publication--The Wet Wallpaper, by Robert Carlton Brown. (Box 79)
- Sketches. (Box 79)
- 4 unidentified folders. (Box 80)
- Advertisement for The Fim Sense (book by Sergei Eisenstein). (Box 80)
- Clippings. (Box 80)
- Clippings, Manuscripts -- 2 Oaxaco stories. (Box 80)
- Clippings--Visual Materials. (Box 80)
- Gastronomy--Recipes, Notes, Clippings on Curry. (Box 80)
- Manuscript--Chess Among the Artists. (Box 80)
- Manuscript--Latin America at Table (for Pan American Magazine). (Box 80)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 80)
- Manusript--History of New York Newspapers. (Box 80)
- Notebook--financial records. (Box 80)
- Notes--scrap paper. (Box 80)
- Stamps. (Box 80)
- Correspondence. (Box 81)
- Drawing--The Sleeve of San Fernando. (Box 81)
- Ephemera. (Box 81)
- Family Correspondence--Bob to Cora Brown. (Box 81)
- Family Correspondence--love letter from Bob Brown to Rose. (Box 81)
- Family Correspondence--Robert Brown (Bob's father) to Cora Brown. (Box 81)
- Family Correspondence--Rose and Bob to Cora Brown, from Germany. (Box 81)
- Gastronomy--Recipes. (Box 81)
- Juvenalia--school assignments. (Box 81)
- Manuscript, Notes, Correspondence--The Complete Book of Cheese. (Box 81)
- Manuscript, Notes--The Machine-made Man. (Box 81)
- Manuscript--autobiographical piece on "Feminist Women". (Box 81)
- Manuscript--Confessions. (Box 81)
- Manuscript--Key of Promise. (Box 81)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 81)
- Manuscript--short story set in Mexico. (Box 81)
- Manuscript--The Empty Cartridge. (Box 81)
- Manuscript--The Lunatic Fringe. (Box 81)
- Manuscript--The Ways of the Wicked. (Box 81)
- Manuscript--The Wooden Headed Nutmeg. (Box 81)
- Notes, Correspondence -- Soviet Trip. (Box 81)
- Notes/Scrap paper. (Box 81)
- Notes--book reviews. (Box 81)
- Archaeological Materials. (Box 82)
- Autobiographical Note--Rose Brown. (Box 82)
- Clippings. (Box 82)
- Clippings--Interview with Gellett Burgess. (Box 82)
- Correspondence. (Box 82)
- Correspondence--Foreign Service re: Rose Brown's Estate. (Box 82)
- Correspondence--Lippincott to Estate of Bob Brown. (Box 82)
- Correspondence--Scott Meredith (literary agent). (Box 82)
- Death Certificate--Rose Brown. (Box 82)
- Drafts, Correspondence, Clippings--Seeds of Hope (Confederate Americans in Brazil). (Box 82)
- Ephemera. (Box 82)
- Gastronomy--Clippings, Correspondence, Notes for the Complete Book of Cheese. (Box 82)
- Gastronomy--Recipes. (Box 82)
- Journal Cover--The American Mercury, ed. H.L. Menken. (Box 82)
- Manuscript--A Country Chauffer Goes to Town. (Box 82)
- Manuscript--A Couple Funerals. (Box 82)
- Manuscript--A Provincial Elegy. (Box 82)
- Manuscript--Bringing Up Chico. (Box 82)
- Manuscript--Demonstration. (Box 82)
- Manuscript--Esquire. (Box 82)
- Manuscript--Exodus, 1937. (Box 82)
- Manuscript--Midnight Tempo, 1935 1/2. (Box 82)
- Manuscript--New Orleans Comes Back. (Box 82)
- Manuscripts (unfinished). (Box 82)
- Manuscript--Southern Discomfort. (Box 82)
- Manuscript--The Inaugural Ceremonies. (Box 82)
- Manuscript--The Slogan Clock. (Box 82)
- Poetry--"Color". (Box 82)
- Poetry--manuscript drafts. (Box 82)
- Publication--Band Concert Night, by Carlton Brown. (Box 82)
- Publicaton--pages from Nomadness. (Box 82)
- Punch. (Box 82)
- Reviews--Brainstorm, by Carlton Brown. (Box 82)
- Animal Drawings. (Box 83)
- Announcement--American Worker's Museum. (Box 83)
- Article--The Sears-Roebuck Saga, by Bob Brown. (Box 83)
- Autobiographical Chronology. (Box 83)
- Booklet--Regions of Brazil (in Portugese). (Box 83)
- Clippings. (Box 83)
- Clippings--"a is for aardvark". (Box 83)
- Clippings--Punch. (Box 83)
- Clippings--Visual Materials. (Box 83)
- Correspondence. (Box 83)
- Ephemera. (Box 83)
- Gastronomy--Clippings, Notes. (Box 83)
- Gastronomy--Cookbook Drafts. (Box 83)
- Gastronomy--Recipes. (Box 83)
- Gastronomy--Rums of Puerto Rico Proposal. (Box 83)
- Memorandum of Agreement--McBride & Co., The Kitchen Book. (Box 83)
- Note--Family Tree. (Box 83)
- Notes, Drafts, Clippings--Recipes from the Portugese. (Box 83)
- Notes/Scrap paper. (Box 83)
- Periodical -- Modern Monthly. (Box 83)
- Periodical--Bolletin de Museo Arqueologico de Colombia. (Box 83)
- Poetry--drafts. (Box 83)
- Real Estate Advertisement--Property in Petropolis. (Box 83)
- Tourism Pamphlet Proposal--on Mines Springs. (Box 83)
- Tourist Booklet--Brazil. (Box 83)
- Clippings. (Box 84)
- Clippings--Car Advertisements. (Box 84)
- Clippings--Punch. (Box 84)
- Correspondence. (Box 84)
- Correspondence--"Ted's Letters". (Box 84)
- Ephemera. (Box 84)
- Gastronomy--Manuscript, Cheeses of All Nations. (Box 84)